In the last lecture, we were able to implement that we are redirected, now however we can see that
Ve uygulayabildiimiz Son Konuma u ki, bununla birlikte fiyatmzn asla bir
our price never is reset once we are redirected, so once we are done, we had that issue before already.
kez yeniden ynlendirildiinde asla sfrlanmadn grebiliriz, nk iimiz bittikten sonra fiyatn asla
Now the price never resets because in our burger builder reducer where we manage the total price,
sfrlanmadn nceden bile biliyoruz, nk Bergere'de Buller veya azaltmak veya toplam fiyat ynettiimiz yerlerde
we only update the price when we add or remove ingredients but we never reset it when we call setIngredients,
sadece katk maddeleri eklediinizde veya kaldrdmzda fiyat gncelleriz ancak set ieriklerini bu set olarak
the setIngredient action is dispatched whenever this page is loaded
adlandrdmzda hibir zaman sfrlamayz Ingrediction, bu sayfa yklendiinde gnderilir.
though, we do it in the burger builder componentDidMount hook and that is on purpose, I want to load
Bergere Boulder bileeninde yapsak da Mt. kanca ve ama ve bir kez benim bileenleri
my ingredients and reset them whenever this component gets mounted.
yklemek ve bu bileen monte alr onlar sfrlamak iin.
Now for that reason since we're doing it here, we have the issue of not updating the price,
u an iin burada yapyoruz, fiyat gncellemeyiz.
we can easily fix this. In the burger builder reducer when we call setIngredients and update the ingredients,
Set malzemeleri belirterek ve malzemeleri yenilediklerinde bunu Burguet Buller redktrnde kolayca dzeltebiliriz.
we simply also have to update the total price and we could get this value from a server too or we simply
Toplam fiyat gncellemek zorundayz ve bu deeri bir sunucudan alabiliriz ya
hardcode it to form which is our initial price up here too. With that if we save this, now we will have an updated
da sadece balang fiyatmz olan 2: 4' ifreleyerek burada tasarruf edersek gncellenmi bir fiyat
price,
alacaz.
so now if I quickly build a delicious cheese bacon burger and just enter any data here to get the job
imdi hzl bir ekilde lezzetli bir peynir pastrmas burger edersen ve ii yapmak iin buraya
done, let's switch to dropdown to mix things up, if I order this, you see the price is now always reset and all
girmek iin herhangi bir veri girdikten sonra hangi eyleri siparie kartrrsanz, fiyat her zaman sfrlamaz ve hepsi
of that without any errors.
de herhangi bir hata yapmaz.
So with that we got the burger builder and the order workflow managed through redux,
Bu yzden Burga bowling ve Reed iin ynetilen sipari i ak aldk.
now of course it's also time to work on the orders page. For that, I'll first of all clear all the orders
phesiz, elbette, ncelikle bor iin sipari sayfasnda almak iin her zaman var, hepsi de tekrar atee kapal
on firebase again.
tm siparileri temizlemek.